his Grey's Anatomy online
fan group probably knows.
(Bernadette:)Is it weird we don't?
(Sheldon:)I don't know.
(Howard:)Maybe the surprise
will make it more fun.
(Howard:)Like magic tricks.
(Howard:)Remember how disappointed
you were
(Howard:)when I explained
the never-ending hanky?
(Bernadette:)I was disappointed to see
the man I was engaged to
(Bernadette:)pulling rainbow scarves
out of his fly.
But how delightful
was it when I pulled out
(Howard:)a bouquet
at the end of those scarves?
(Howard:)It'll be the same thing
(Howard:)when the doctor pulls
a beautiful surprise out of you.
(Bernadette:)Everyone said I could do better.
(Howard:)But you didn't listen,
and presto change-o,
my baby's inside you. Ta-da!
(Amy (off):)Ugh. What is that?